Welcome to the HeliosX Logistics Hub — where pharmaceutical excellence meets operational efficiency.
Every day, stock arrives from our pharmaceutical partners — carefully received and immediately processed into our secure facility.
Our dedicated Royal Mail elevated ramp ensures priority postal integration for high-volume dispatch.
Inside our climate-controlled facility, every product is tracked, stored, and maintained to pharmaceutical standards.
Three specialized packaging lines serve our key brands.
Dermatica — processed on a dedicated line with white and green branding for precise dermatology treatments.
MedExpress — prepared on a fast-throughput blue line for rapid nationwide dispatch.
ZipHealth — fulfilled on a dedicated digital-health line alongside MedExpress operations.
Completed orders move to our collections bays for nationwide delivery via partners and carriers.
HeliosX — powering pharmaceutical logistics from receipt to delivery. Excellence in every step. As part of the HeliosX Group, we’re building the future of digital healthcare — from online consultations to your doorstep. Trusted. Efficient. HeliosX.